Tristan Sabado

Motion & Editorial Designer

I am here to make design approachable. I use a process of research, iteration and discussions to create something authentic to your vision. Whether it's a sleek video, an engaging booklet, or a cohesive visual identity to your brand, the end result will carry your voice out into the world. With my detail-oriented work ethic and flexibility, I will find the best solutions for your ideas and make them tangible.

education

2018–2022 York University & Sheridan College Program in Design (YSDN)

Honours Bachelor of Design | Magna Cum Laude

2014–2018 Mary Ward CSS

High School Diploma

work history

2021 Room Edit by Stacey Cohen — 3 Month Internship

Graphic Designer/Video Editor

- · Migrated and updated deck template from Illustrator to InDesign
- Collaborated with other marketing interns to construct and tailor decks to potential partners with the new template
- Collaborated with other marketing interns to expand the single deck template into a set of six for different types of collaborations/partnerships using InDesign
- · Animated short promotional ads/materials using After Effects and Premiere Pro
- Animated a step by step explanatory video on the process of Room Edit's interior design using After Effects and Premiere Pro
- Worked with my Supervisor using Squarespace to create a hub with training modules for the on-boarding process for new interior designers
 - Created and organized web pages and links
 - Organized, revised and updated documents and information on spreadsheets
 - Made icon sets using Illustrator
 - · Edited video footage and touched up audio for each module using *Premiere Pro*
 - · Animated cohesive opening and ending slates for each module using After Effects
 - · Coordinated headshots and bio acquisition for core team members
- Worked with the Director of Room Edit's parent company Stacey Cohen Design, using Wordpress to create a hub with an organized and categorized list of vendors for their interior designers similar to Room Edit's hub

2018 Mary Ward CSS — Commission

Editorial Designer

- Co-designer for the 2018–2019 school agenda for use by both students and staff
 - · Revised and consolidated rules, guidelines, and other formal information
 - Constructed the daily planner in accordance to the provided calendar using Photoshop and Indesign

extracurriculars & volunteering

2018–2019	York University YU Esports
	Mary Ward CSS
2014–2018	Anime Association
	Co-leader 2017-2018
2017	Spain Concert Band Tour
	Performed in Barcelona, Alicante, Seville & Madrid
2016–2017	Leader/Extended Leader (Grade 9 Orientation Program)
2014-2018	Chess Club
2010–2015	John Lau Taekwon-do
	Achieved 2nd degree black belt

Student Teacher | 2013-2015

contact details

(647) 895-8747 thetadsn846@gmail.com 85 Maresfield Drive Scarborough ON MIV 2W9

Portfolio

https://sabadot.github.jo/

SKILLS

Adobe Software

refer to software experience

Data Research/AnalysisTCPS2 core certified

Leadership Experience

Photography/Video Capture

SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

- · After Effects
- · Premiere Pro
- · InDesign
- · Photoshop
- · Illustrator
- · HTML/CSS
- · Squarespace
- · Wordpress
- GarageBand
- Audacity
- Animate

references available upon request